Please don't ask.
聞かないでください
went?
行 った?
Please don't ask.
聞かないでください
Why do you ask?
なんで聞くの?
It might be quiet.
静かかもしれない
Peace to the camera.
カメラに向かってピースして
Peace to the camera?
カメラに向かってピースして?
Yeah, peace.
うん、ピースして
Lay your elbows down?
ひじついた状態を伏せる?
How should I go?
どうやって行こうか?
Lay down here?
ここ に寝転んで?
Lie down on your side?
横に寝転んで?
What happened?
どうなってた?
It's getting hard.
硬くなってる
What happened?
どうなってた?
Is it getting bigger?
大きくなってる?
Can I have you sit and lick my prick again?
もう一回、チクミ舐めながら座ってもらっていい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Open your legs.
足を開けて
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Don't do it.
しないで
If you could do it live, I would have done my best.
生でしてくれたら、 頑 張 っちゃった
Can you open your legs and put your hands between them?
足を開けて、 両手を足の間に入れられる?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I don't do it at times like this.
こんなときはしないもんね
Can you open your legs and close them a little more?
足を開けて、もうちょっと足閉じられる?
Only the upper body fell down.
上半身だけ、 倒れて
Only the upper body.
上半身だけ
It rang.
鳴っちゃったね
It's cute.
可愛 いじゃん
It rang.
鳴っちゃった
It really rang.
本当に鳴っちゃった
Are you concerned?
懸念してる?
I'm concerned.
懸念してる
I've had a lot.
いっぱいいっちゃったもんな
Were you concerned?
懸念した?
I went out, but it was too small.
出たんだけどさ、 なんか狭すぎてさ、
I don't come, not much.
来ないわ、あんまり
It's going to be dangerous if it stays like this, so I'll just have 2 items or something.
このままだとやばいから、 2品とかで
Wait for the fourth one, here.
4つ目待って、ここで
Get up completely,
完全に起き上がって、
Will you come?
来 ない?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
Maybe it all went to the back.
全部奥に行っちゃったかも
It came out a little, but I guess it only came out quietly.
ちょっと出たんだけど、 そっとしか出たかな?
Are you okay?
大丈夫なの?
I think it's okay to stand up.
立っても大丈夫だと思うから
This position,
こっちの位置さ、
Shall I pin it?
ピ ンスしよっか